how to pay your sun life insurance
policy using video online banking
first you must log in your account
and on the lower right click more
look for enrollment services
[Music]
click enroll company or biller
fill out
for a company or builder
choose sun life of canada philippines
incorporated
[Music]
for subscriber number
write your policy number
or also include your name
unsubscriber name just put your name
for your prepared nickname
you can use also your policy number and
your full name
or just input sun life insurance
[Music]
now click continue
we can go now to
pay bills
fill out bills payments pay from pick
your account and pay this company or
dealer
choose you enrolled earlier which is sun
life of canada philippines incorporated
input the amount you want to pay
for the remarks type your complete name
and policy number
finally click continue
then double check and click confirm
[Music]
congratulations we're done
you